<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Eric T Cormack</title>
    <link>//erictcormack.com/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Eric T Cormack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="//erictcormack.com/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//erictcormack.com/resume/compsci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//erictcormack.com/resume/compsci/</guid>
      <description> Coursework in cognitive science, database design, natural language processing et al. Studied iOS and Swift, including UIKit, Grand Central Dispatch, Auto Layout and Foundation Created a couplet generator using NLP concepts such as the hidden Markov model Developed a game proof-of-concept in a studio-team setting Geographic Information Systems project chosen for DePaul’s Map of the Month, March 2017  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//erictcormack.com/resume/erikson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//erictcormack.com/resume/erikson/</guid>
      <description> Developed and documented guidelines for deploying Apple computers throughout the organization, allowing for standardized user experience for Apple users in a Windows business environment Debugged WordPress, PHP, SQL and JavaScript issues to ensure uninterrupted web service Corrected a range of technical issues including AV, printer/copier and critical hardware failure  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//erictcormack.com/resume/milyli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//erictcormack.com/resume/milyli/</guid>
      <description> Contributed to the development of Milyli products, such as Blackout, adding to the codebase and taking a lead point on design and user experience. Built a prototype of a product for the Relativity platform, laying the foundation of a future Milyli development project. Engineered a Slack bot for Milyli&amp;rsquo;s product team, to highlight build status and engage the team in creating quality code.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//erictcormack.com/resume/miraclemessages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//erictcormack.com/resume/miraclemessages/</guid>
      <description> Modified and created data models and view controllers to comply with new database changes Release with contributed code available in the App Store  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>